maximonline.com 2018-12-30

# Maxim

Updated September 23, 2014

This Privacy Policy explains how Maxim. (“Maxim”) stores and uses personal and non-personal information provided by you to us or collected by us in any manner. Some examples

\- through our Site (as defined below);

\- mobile applications (such as those available on [iPhone](http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=nb_sb_noss_2?url=search-alias%3daps&field-keywords=iphone&rh=i%3aaps%2ck%3aiphone), iPad, Android, and other smart phone or table devices);

\- applications on other computer or Internet based platforms (e.g., Those operating on videogame systems, set-top devices or smart tv's);

\- telephone calls, emails, mail or other communication and content (such as pictures, video or other information) you provide us via the above or in non-electronic formats.

As used herein, “ ** _Site_** ” refers to [www.maxim.com](http://www.maxim.com/) and other sites on the World Wide Web (including sites designed to be accessed by browsers using Wireless Application Protocol) originating in the United States, if they are owned and/or operated by Maxim.

By accessing and using the Site, mobile applications, or other applications (collectively, “ **Digital Devices** ”) you expressly accept and agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in the Privacy Policy (“ ** _Policy_** ”) and you understand any non-electronic or analog communications will be treated the same. If you do not wish to be bound by the Policy, you have no license to use our Digital Devices and should leave the Site or cease use of our other Digital Devices immediately.

Maxim reserves the right to modify the Policy in any way, at any time. Any and all such modifications will take effect immediately after Maxim provides reasonable notice. Notice may be given by any of the following: posting on Digital Devices; via electronic communication; in writing; and/or any other means that provides reasonable notice. _Your further use of Digital Devices after such reasonable notice has been provided constitutes your acceptance of the modified Policy._

1\. Personally-Identifying Information

Maxim, directly and through third parties (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, or vendors with whom we work), collects personally-identifying information in many places throughout our Digital Devices, for example: (a) when you register for the online newsletter or magazine subscriber-only area of Digital Devices, (b) enter contests and sweepstakes and participate in other online activities (including, but not limited to, surveys, chat rooms, games, and bulletin boards, or make a purchase in our online store), and/or (c) provide us [Submitted Content](http://www.maxim.com/corporate/terms-conditions#submitted-content). If you elect to connect your third-party website account (e.g., Facebook), you should assume that personally-identifying information contained in your profile at such third-party website (but not your password) will be provided to us. This personally-identifying information may include your picture, name, address (street address, city, state, and zip code), contact information (e.g., e-mail address and telephone numbers), and other identifiers that permit Maxim and/or third parties to contact you directly, gather information about you, or identify you.

Maxim uses personally-identifying information to award prizes and/or, with your permission, for promotional and marketing purposes. Maxim uses this information and outside records to offer promotions, products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such offers from Maxim, please email [newsletters@maxim.com](mailto:newsletters@maxim.com) with the subject line UNSUBSCRIBE ME. _**Your “Unsubscribe” efforts can be undone by you if you enter another contest or opt into marketing communications in the future.**_

Maxim may also, from time-to-time, make personally-identifying information available to other companies so that they may also offer promotions, products, programs, and/or services of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive such offers from other companies, email [offers@maxim.com](mailto:offers@maxim.com) with the subject line UNSUBSCRIBE ME. _**Your “Unsubscribe” efforts can be undone by you if you enter another contest or opt into marketing communications in the future.**_

Maxim may also disclose personally-identifying information in response to legal process, such as a request by law enforcement, a court order or subpoena, or to protect the integrity of the Site if Maxim believes that a guest has committed unlawful or otherwise harmful acts.

If any individual submits content for publication, Maxim may publish his or her name and any other information submitted by that individual. 

If guests elect to use any provided "E-mail to a Friend" referral service for informing a friend about this Site, Maxim asks for the friend's e-mail address and then sends an e-mail inviting the friend to visit the Site. This information is stored by the Site for the sole purpose of sending this e-mail invitation.

In addition, Maxim may share or disclose personally-identifying information about you to other companies or individuals if any of the following occur:

i. You provide us with Submitted Content>;

ii. Maxim uses third party service providers to provide products, services, content or functions on its behalf. In instances where they are providing work at our specific direction (e.g., sending emails, processing credit cards, or fulfilling subscriptions) we ask them to not use such information for any reason except to carry out the purposes for which Maxim hired them. In other instances where Maxim has not hired the third party provider (e.g., Facebook or Twitter widgets on our Digital Devices), these service providers maintain their own privacy policies with regards to your personally-identifying information;

iii. You have entered a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by a third party and you have agreed to permit the third party to share, disclose or otherwise use personally-identifying information, in which case the information may be shared with that third party for their use as permitted by their respective privacy policies, including direct marketing; 

iv. Maxim needs to protect its legal rights (such as collecting money owed to Maxim) 

v. Maxim must comply with applicable laws, regulations, and/or legal or regulatory process; 

vi. In connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (of assets, stock, or otherwise) of all or a portion of the business conducted by the Digital Devices.

2\. Non-Personally-Identifying Information

Maxim, directly and through third parties, collects non-personally identifying information for purposes of Digital Devices administration and to compile aggregate information about usage of Digital Devices including by way of example, via widgets, beacons and cookies. For an example of how Maxim uses a third party service to collect and use non-personally identifying information on the Site, click here: <http://www.nielsen-netratings.com/privacy/sitecensus.htm>

We may take your Personal Information and make it non-personally identifying, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you (de-personalizing your information). Maxim also shares this aggregate, non-personally identifying information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes.

3\. Purchase Information

If you purchase a product from a third party or from the Digital Devices, information may be collected from you (possibly including, but not limited to, credit card and contact information) by third party providers facilitating our e-commerce store. Maxim does not receive or retain any credit card information, though we do receive and retain your name, shipping/billing addresses and order details. Unless otherwise stated, Maxim does not have any responsibility in connection with such purchases and all transactions and use of any customer information are the sole responsibility of the product provider. Be sure to review the product provider's privacy policy and contact them directly if you have any questions. They may have privacy terms that differ from Maxim's Privacy Policy

4\. IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you log on to the Web. When you request pages from the Site, web servers automatically identify and log your computer’s IP address.

Maxim collects guests’ IP addresses only for the purpose of system administration and to report aggregate information to advertisers, corporate affiliates, consultants, and/or third parties who perform a particular service for Maxim. Maxim does not combine IP addresses with other personally-identifying information or compile any session activity reports by IP address.

5\. Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you are online. The use of cookies is an industry standard. You will find them at most major Web sites.

Maxim uses cookies to determine which areas of the Site are popular and which are not, and to manage functionality on our site. This helps Maxim to target ads based on guest interests, and also improve and update the Site based on such data as total number of guests and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies.

A cookie allows Maxim to store the personal preferences that you set during each visit to the Site, which in turn speeds up your future activities at the Site. Similarly, the stores hosted by the Site usually use cookies to track which products you have chosen to purchase while shopping. Letting cookies do the record-keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again.

You may occasionally get cookies from Maxim’s advertisers on the Site as well. The Site does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to the Policy. Advertisers do not have access to the Site's cookies. 

The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You may be able to direct your browser to refuse cookies or alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the Site, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

6\. Third-Party Advertisers

Maxim uses third party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on its behalf when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the following web addresses: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> <http://www.advertising.com/Privacy.html> <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy>. If you are using our mobile applications on an Apple iPhone or iPad, you may opt-out by pointing your device’s browser to the Apple opt-out page (<http://oo.apple.com/>). Note that even if you elect to opt-out, you will still see general advertisements.

If we are part of a business transaction like a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of some or all of our assets, your personal information may be included among the assets transferred. If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your Personal Information is collected or used. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any such acquiring party may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Minors (individuals under 18 years of age) should always ask parents for permission before providing any personal information online. No information should be submitted to or posted on the Digital Devices by any Minor without the consent of a parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Maxim does not knowingly provide any personally-identifying information about Minors, regardless of its source, to third parties, nor is this information knowingly used by Maxim for any marketing or promotional purposes. Minors are not allowed to participate in contests on the Digital Devices.

Our website is intended for general audiences over the age of 18 and is not directed to children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13, we will delete that user's personal information from our databases.

Whenever you disclose information online in chat rooms, message boards, or similar posting areas, that information can be viewed, collected, and used by anyone. Therefore, do not disclose any information in such areas that you do not want made available to the general public. Maxim is not responsible for the consequences of such disclosures including, but not limited to, unsolicited communications.

The Site has implemented appropriate safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and to make proper use of the information that Maxim collects. Nevertheless, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be completely secure. Thus, while Maxim will use commercially reasonable security measures to protect your personal information, it cannot absolutely guarantee the security of any information that you provide. Maxim is not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may misappropriate any such information.

To unsubscribe from the Maxim Online newsletter and/or other electronic communications from Maxim, reply to the e-mail newsletters with “UNSUBSCRIBE” (and only “UNSUBSCRIBE”) in the subject line or follow the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the e-mail. You can also unsubscribe from promotional and marketing e-mails that you receive from Site partners by typing “UNSUBSCRIBE” (and only “UNSUBSCRIBE”) in the subject line in a reply to one of the Site partner’s e-mails to you or by following the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the e-mail.

To change the address of your Maxim Magazine subscription, or to provide any other subscription-related information to Maxim, you may write to Maxim, P.O. Box 420235, Palm Coast, FL 3214, or call 1(386)447-6312.

Under California law, our users that are California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. This request may be made by each person only once per year. Such requests must be submitted to us by email at [mlegal@maxim.com](mailto:mlegal@maxim.com), or by mail at Maxim Inc. Attn: California Privacy Laws, 415 Madison Ave, 4th floor, New York, NY 10017. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the email or postal address specified above.

Please direct any comments or questions regarding Maxim’s Privacy Policy to Maxim Inc., Privacy Policy, 415 Madison Ave, 4th floor, New York, NY 10017.
